## **System Support Engineer III**

# ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume
Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama

## **Objective**

Desire a position as a System Support Engineer with a company where my Wireless RF, PCS experience and Data Network skills can be used to minimize circuit down time and increase company network productivity, as expand knowledge of VOIP/WAN networks.

#### Skills

C#, SQL, Windows Server.

## Work Experience

## **System Support Engineer III**

ABC Corporation - December 1998 - October 1999

- Provided 24/7 NOC engineering and technical assistance for customer multi-protocol, multiservice switching platforms.
- Built point to multi-point circuit connections.
- Programed NMS terminals, routers and catalyst switches.
- Analyzed packet switch crash vectors and data base software integrity.
- Tested Cisco 7500 series routers and 5000 series catalyst switch configurations in lab setting.
- · Performed IP address and subnet mask allocation.
- Used routing protocols OSPF, BGP, IGRP and EIGRP.

### **System Support Engineer**

**Delta Corporation** - 1997 - 1998

- Include driving to customer location to deploy and maintain servers and networking equipment.
- Resource to PC Technicians in the field; product research and purchasing recommendations.
- Was providing services and support for Unix/Linux system to maintain system integrity, back up, restore data, troubleshoot faults, tuning, monitoring.
- Attend the critical fault calls from clients on Windows NT / 2000 stations.
- Server Support October 2014 Present 2012 File and print server infrastructure update Created Powershell scripts to Migrate From 2008 to 2012 File .
- Patching windows servers with SCCM On-Call Duties Dell Hardware support Manage 1200 servers Vmware support Document process for Tier 2 and 3.
- Desktop Support August 2011 January 2012.

### **Education**

Bachelor's- (Cape Fear Community College)